Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/shankar-ekbhagu-917a31156 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Electrical Maintenance Model-based Systems Engineering (MBSE)

System of Systems Engineering

Shankar ekbhagu

electrical engineer at mahindra cie automotive Ltd Pune, Maharashtra, India

Summary

i have 10 year experience in electrical and mechanical maintenance. i have basic and practical knowledge about electrical components operations and testing. also i have knowledge of plc system reading and making new program also my fault finding knowledge is excellent.

Experience

mahindra cie automotive Ltd pune Electrical Maintenance Engineer May 2018 - Present (5 years 4 months) Pune, Maharashtra, India

electrical and mechanical maintenance handles

Kirloskar Ferrous Industries Limited System Engineer August 2011 - May 2018 (6 years 10 months) Solapur, Maharashtra, India

electrical and mechanical maintenance handles

Education

government polytechnic osmanabad diploma in electrical, technical (2008 - 2011)

hanuman highschool tandulwadi ssc, full · (2007 - 2007)